naijamayor.com 2012-12-18

# Privacy Policy | NIGERIA ENTERTAINMENT | Top Nigeria Entertainment Site

It is our policy to respect the privacy of the people who access and use our network of websites, including the site you linked from (the “Site”) and the services we provide to you on the Site (Naijamayor.com).  This Privacy Policy applies to information that you provide to us through the Site and our Services, and when you access, download or use any information, services, products or content appearing on the Site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site.

**What information do we collect?**

We (Naijamayor.com) collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or contact us, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

_To send periodic  emails_  
The email address you provide, will only be used to send you information and updates. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Cookies?**

We may uses cookies on certain pages of our service. Cookies are small pieces of information that your Web browser places on your computers hard drive. Cookies can help us personalize our Web site and provide information that is targeted to the interests of individual Users so you don’t see the same advertisements repeatedly.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our site Naijamayor.com.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection**

We do not direct the Site to persons under 13 years of age, and requires Users to be 13 years or older. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect or maintain on the Site personally identifying or other information from persons under 13 years of age.  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact mayorbosspromo@gmail.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our site and Services may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

This policy was last modified on July 2012

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

### mayorbosspromo@gmail.com  
skype: mayor boss  
Facebook: mayorboss  
Twitter: nigeriahiphop

Feel Free, Share! with Your Friends

  * More

**Do you have a story for publication? Please email it to mayorbosspromo@gmail.com** **Like & Get Update on Facebook Now **
